http://www.midi-store.com/terms_privacy.asp

Go!
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also collect specific information about winning contest recipients so that we can fulfill the prize to them.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
We also collect information about winning contest recipients so that we can fulfill their prize to them. When you enter a contest or other give away, you give us your permission to communicate your name to other entrants if you are the winner. In addition if you win a contest or give away, we may ask you for an email or video testimonial about your experience as the contest winner for marketing purposes.
How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. We will not transmit any personal identifiable information to these third party service providers. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include The Midi Store LLC. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you (such as delivery services, or manufacturer technical support), so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.How can you opt-out, modify or delete information that you have provided to us?To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. You may also click the unsubscribe link a the bottom of marketing email you have received. Your changes should be immediate but in no case longer than 24 hours. To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site (such as, but not limited to: videos, manufacturer links and similar.)
These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on May 22nd, 2018Questions and feedbackWe welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue through the contact us page
Entire PolicyThis privacy policy applies to information collected through our website as well as any information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentAs or May 25,2018, by using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Subscribe to our mailing list
Email Address
We Accept
Company Info
About Us
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
My Account
Returns & Exchanges
var ju_num="562B5009-442A-447D-BBE4-8FFBD18DDCDE";var asset_host=(("https:"==document.location.protocol)?"https":"http")+'://d2j3qa5nc37287.cloudfront.net/';(function() {var s=document.createElement('script');s.type='text/javascript';s.async=true;s.src=asset_host+'coupon_code1.js';var x=document.getElementsByTagName('script')[0];x.parentNode.insertBefore(s,x);})();
Copyright © 1993-2020 The Midi Store. All Rights Reserved.
